&GT；&GT；Kyle：那么ToNumber呢？
&gt;&gt; Kyle: So what about ToNumber?
这个更有趣，因为涉及到更多的角落案件。
This one's a bit more interesting cuz there's a lot more corner cases involved.
任何时候，我们需要做一些数字，但我们没有一个数字，
Anytime we need to do something numeric and we don't have a number,
我们将调用ToNumber抽象操作。
we're gonna invoke the ToNumber abstract operation.
那么有哪些例子呢？
So what are some examples of those?
他们中的一些人格式很好，但他们中的一些人是奇怪的。
Some of them are well formed, but some of them are strange.
空线，我想，是最让我抓狂的。
Empty string, I think, is the one that drives me the most bonkers.
空字符串，无论何时进行数字编码，或
Empty string, whenever numericofied, or
不管合适的词是什么，都变成了0。
whatever the right word would be for that, becomes 0.
现在就我而言
Now as far as I'm concerned,
空字符串是你说我在字符串中没有值的方式。
empty string is the way that you say I have no values in a string.
这是因为该类型中没有任何字符串值。
It's the absence of any string value within that type.
没有其他表示字符串类型中缺少值的表示，
There's no other representation of the absence of values within the string type,
据我所知，除了空字符串之外。
other than an empty string, as far as I can tell.
所以如果是价值的缺失，为什么要这么做，当它变成一个数字时，
So if it's the absence of value, why on Earth does it, when it becomes a number,
变成一个像数字0一样的实际数字，而不是已经存在的数字
become an actual number like the number 0 instead of the number that already exist
在语言中，这表示我们没有一个有效的数字？
in the language, that represents we don't have a valid number?
应该是南。
Which would have been NaN.
我在这一点上大声疾呼是因为事实证明，
I'm ranting on this particular point because it turns out,
我们将看到这是JavaScript中所有邪恶的根源。
we're gonna see that's the root of all evil in JavaScript.
但其余大部分都是非常明智的。
But most of the rest of these are all very sensible.
如果您有字符串0，它将变为0。
If you had the string 0, it becomes 0.
如果你有字符串-0，这里有一个惊喜，它实际上变成了-0，
If you had the string -0, here's a surprise, it actually becomes -0,
很酷。
very cool.
它去掉了任何前导空格、尾随空格和
It strips off any leading white space, trailing whitespace, and
前导零，所以我们只得到9。
leading zeros, so we just get 9.
它可以很好地处理浮点。
It handles floating points well.
关于尾部和前导圆点的一些奇怪之处，但是
Some weirdness with the trailing and leading dots, but
这些在句法上是有效的。
those are syntactically valid.
它甚至处理其他的基数，就像本例中的十六进制一样。
It even handles other's bases, like in this case, hexadecimal.
所以数字，我不知道这个词应该是什么，
So the numerification, I don't know what that word should be,
字符串值是相当合理的，有几种奇怪的角点情况。
of a string value is fairly sensible, with a couple of weird corner cases.
如何处理错误或错误的数值化
What about dealing with the numerification of falses or
TRUE、NULL或UNDEFINED？
trues, or nulls or undefined?
其他的原语呢？
What about those other primitives?
好的，假变成0，真变成1。
Well, false becomes 0, true becomes 1.
在开始的时候，你可能会想，嗯，这是完全有道理的。
And at the outset, you might think, well, that makes complete sense.
从历史上看，我们一直认为假是0，
Historically, we've always thought of false as being 0 and
从逐位的角度来看，为1为真。
true as being 1, from bit-wise perspective.
我要走了，我要坚定地说那是个糟糕的主意，
I'm gonna go, I'm gonna put my foot down and say that was a terrible idea,
该假和真，当表示为数字时，应该表示为NaN。
that false and true, when represented as numbers should have represented as NaN.
稍后你就会明白为什么。
And you'll see why a little bit later.
但是那个，我不喜欢这个决定。
But that, I don't like that decision.
但我理解为什么在更大的规划范围内，
But I understand why, within the context of greater programming,
这可能是大多数人所期待的。
that's probably what most people would expect.
NULL变成0，好吗？
Null becomes 0, okay?
但是undefined变成NaN，什么？
But undefined becomes NaN, what?
在这里，他们最终决定使用NaN，但他们没有将其与null一起使用？
Here they decided to finally use NaN, but they didn't use it with null?
谁来给我解释一下。
Somebody explain that one to me.
null应该是NaN，就像undefined应该是NaN一样。
Null should have been NaN, just like undefined should have been NaN.
好的，所以当我们对不是字符串的非原语使用ToNumber时，
Okay, so when we use ToNumber on a nonprimitive that's not a string,
或者不是未定义的，或者是布尔值或其他什么，当我们在对象中使用它时，
or not an undefined, or a boolean or whatever, when we use it in an object,
记住，它用数字提示唤起了ToPrimitive。
remember it evokes the ToPrimitive with the number hint.
如果您还记得，它首先参考的是的值，并且
And if you recall, that consults first the valueOf, and
然后它查询toString。
then it consults the toString.
那看起来像什么？
So what does that look like?
嗯，对于任何数组或对象，默认情况下，意味着您
Well, for any array or object, by default, meaning you
没有覆盖这些，valueOf方法本质上只是返回本身。
have not overridden these, the valueOf method essentially just returns itself.
它本质上是这样做的，返回这个。
It essentially does this, return this.
其具有仅仅忽略value of并延迟到toString的影响。
Which has the affect of just ignoring the valueOf and deferring to toString.
所以暗示是数字并不重要。
So it doesn’t even matter that the hint was number.
它只是直接进入toString。
It just goes directly to the toString.
你可以认为一个物体的编号是，
You can think of the numberification of an object as,
本质上，它的串行化。
essentially, the stringification of it.
它最终会产生任何toString或value of产生的结果。
It's that it's gonna end up producing whatever toString or valueOf produces.
这是一个令人费解的选择，但它仍然是一个选择，
That's a perplexing choice, but it's the choice nonetheless,
它实际上会产生一个原始字符串。
is that it's gonna actually produce a primitive string.
因此，在您的各种操作中，您希望得到一个原语，但是
So then in your various operations where you were expecting a primitive, but
你想要一个本原数字，那里实际上有一个原语字符串。
you wanted a primitive number, there's actually a primitive string there.
然后进一步的胁迫就会发生。
And then further coersions will kick in.
所以我们最终会遵循toString
So we're gonna end up deferring to the toString and
toString返回的内容。
whatever the toString returns.
记住数组是如何在没有任何括号的情况下对自身进行Stringify的。
Remember how arrays toStringify themselves without any brackets.
同样，我们得到一个包含空字符串的数组。
So again, we get an array with an empty string in it.
当我们对它进行编号时，它最终是0，这是胡说八道。
When we ToNumber it, it ends up as 0, which is nuts.
然后是包含0的字符串，变成0更有意义。
And then the string with 0 in it, becoming 0 makes a lot more sense.
而-0则更有意义。
And -0 makes a lot more sense.
这里有件奇怪的事情。
Here's something bizarre.
如果数组为NULL或未定义，则为0。
If the array has either null or undefined, it becomes 0.
看看你有没有注意到。
See if you're paying attention.
有人能告诉我为什么这里这两个都变成0吗？
Can anyone tell me why both of those become 0 here?
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：与其余部分不一致-
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Not consistent with the rest of the-
&gt；&gt；Kyle：实际上，这是非常显著的
&gt;&gt; Kyle: Actually, this is remarkably
与我们已经看到的其他疯狂一致。
consistent with the other craziness we've already seen.
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：因为它们首先变成空字符串？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Because they first become empty strings?
&gt；&gt；Kyle：它们首先变成空字符串，然后空字符串变成0。
&gt;&gt; Kyle: They first become empty strings, and then empty string becomes 0.
记住，空字符串是所有强迫邪恶的根源，好吗？
Remember, empty string is the root of all coercion evil, okay?
空字符串变成0是所有强制邪恶的根源，好吗？
Empty string becoming 0 is the root of all coercion evil, okay?
下面那个疯狂的嵌套数组也是一样的，
Same thing with that bottom crazy nested array thing,
它只是变成一个空字符串，然后变成0，好吗？
it just becomes an empty string, which then just becomes 0, okay?
&gt；&gt；Kyle：好的，如果你有一个对象，它的toString返回对象。
&gt;&gt; Kyle: All right, so if you have an object, its toString returns the object.
并且记住默认情况下对象的字符串标识是什么，
And remember what a stringification of an object by default is,
是那个方括号的东西。
it's that square bracket object object thing.
这肯定不是一个数字的表示，所以我们得到NaN。
Which is definitely not a representation of a number, so we get NaN.
这实际上是合理的。
That's actually reasonable.
这是愚蠢的，但它是合理的。
It's dumb, but it's reasonable.
如果重写某个对象的value of，
If you override the valueOf for some object,
你可以归还任何你想要的东西。
you can return whatever thing you want.
在本例中，您可以返回3，这就是它的编号。
In this case, you could return 3, and that's the numberification for it.